[
  {
    "question": "1x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "64a833e3-6a5c-4772-8036-6bc86697200c"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x1",
    "answer": "1",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "192522e5-1f0a-4dcf-ac7c-fc34cb291b2e"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x2",
    "answer": "2",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "4a8ad079-5392-45ea-9fdb-f0ffbaf21f8f"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x3",
    "answer": "3",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "bdaac741-0260-4b1f-a1d1-caed929243ca"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x4",
    "answer": "4",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "f9ce6f47-e235-4c6f-a9cf-e8de80dc573a"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x5",
    "answer": "5",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "2dbf805a-7566-4dc5-a59d-b2e94d0d2544"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x6",
    "answer": "6",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "4302d255-9906-434b-bb33-5a300ef6c014"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x7",
    "answer": "7",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "d529f568-6bde-4664-938d-4608e8fa5b04"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x8",
    "answer": "8",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "6d061cbb-2ef3-449b-a8bc-5d76bf0021ff"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x9",
    "answer": "9",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "06b104a4-109a-4f41-bb96-50f51e059889"
  },
  {
    "question": "1x10",
    "answer": "10",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "e9556721-afc5-4cb2-ae9e-a7d4d6116352"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "bc1a0016-da30-4c85-bd91-fd63331a37f2"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x1",
    "answer": "2",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "da56d152-c071-4c71-8f79-0eba9942243a"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x2",
    "answer": "4",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "fa83cf62-4300-4ee6-8cb3-5d3145ade464"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x3",
    "answer": "6",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "7eb7da34-c56a-4787-b5be-c92eef312b21"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x4",
    "answer": "8",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "c512cac8-c728-4658-8a7e-ad7c676d6a12"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x5",
    "answer": "10",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "492529ee-d4e3-496a-8cf0-10b7f600afd8"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x6",
    "answer": "12",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "15c43e15-8255-4e45-8c96-f4812f80fce0"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x7",
    "answer": "14",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "0c6348fb-54a1-4257-94ba-aa3e55629cf2"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x8",
    "answer": "16",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "879c6108-f84a-4fe9-b744-828dfeddf209"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x9",
    "answer": "18",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3e0ed4fa-9e1c-4be4-b9cd-e6ab0cf31fae"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x10",
    "answer": "20",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "cdd5ccdf-eaf5-4c68-af4b-1738c8ff8b60"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "dde3da4a-6c72-4983-a7f2-9210e8f99028"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x1",
    "answer": "3",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "74a98826-eac9-4c77-8acb-83a779a2373e"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x2",
    "answer": "6",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "883a17b6-95a0-4256-9559-437d162e9dd7"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x3",
    "answer": "9",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "9bdc172a-ca1f-4506-a9c1-9ed2a8a0fc28"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x4",
    "answer": "12",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "22f4a6a3-d5e2-4ef4-af18-a40d6df95b54"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x5",
    "answer": "15",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "63ab861e-9aca-4e50-99ba-c8dddf8cdb58"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x6",
    "answer": "18",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "9e69d800-dfa3-4d31-a52a-3bcb5dcc40ce"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x7",
    "answer": "21",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "e3d44ec8-b435-4ee5-bc9d-2c1c138c20bc"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x8",
    "answer": "24",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "6d0e1a34-70c1-4671-9da9-f9d8d56ac1c7"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x9",
    "answer": "27",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "ed87d240-ebbf-4231-81e9-8b7f4a373efa"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x10",
    "answer": "30",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "0c8134ba-4ed4-4bfd-9829-102bf71e8b58"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "53188228-d052-4b85-b3be-b735c442fc7b"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x1",
    "answer": "4",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "ef787ed2-2639-46ec-be23-d7fbd40ad562"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x2",
    "answer": "8",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "5932bf45-d61d-4245-9f73-8e369d28dbac"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x3",
    "answer": "12",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "9c42acf8-a79d-4808-9741-1b1643173482"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x4",
    "answer": "16",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "63f27cc8-29b2-406f-b3b4-85a13690579c"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x5",
    "answer": "20",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "b829ecbe-962a-431e-bd70-34f5708d52a5"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x6",
    "answer": "24",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "9141835c-38aa-4499-9266-a1d8cb51cf26"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x7",
    "answer": "28",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "b51bb35a-cf1f-4666-8992-37785037d842"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x8",
    "answer": "32",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3ab99457-eafc-4a93-b0a1-d525ac5884c0"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x9",
    "answer": "36",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "42471894-58f1-4b3a-b15d-609226b355b6"
  },
  {
    "question": "4x10",
    "answer": "40",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a25fb113-b71d-4e88-87ee-59ec0c7cc782"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "cad5bf81-fd1b-4946-b627-b0af81e9ba8a"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x1",
    "answer": "5",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "ffbe5f6d-04e4-4874-8b06-43d3d69f05b3"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x2",
    "answer": "10",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "fc322dd7-ac8e-4bb2-942f-d43dd989d261"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x3",
    "answer": "15",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "8e33498c-0f25-4b13-ad12-ab9c9f23d93b"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x4",
    "answer": "20",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "71f5d812-3a06-4d90-8f7e-fc4920922509"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x5",
    "answer": "25",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "da126249-dbbc-45ec-abf2-a12f59de17bd"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x6",
    "answer": "30",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "6d57177d-6430-4bb8-bb70-b4acf6340a2c"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x7",
    "answer": "35",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "dfe4de3b-0678-4821-94bc-c0b3aeaafb72"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x8",
    "answer": "40",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "4a417eac-2c1b-4cb4-947d-bfcae8583c46"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x9",
    "answer": "45",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "f09b1bd4-dbc9-4301-a828-519907bdfb0b"
  },
  {
    "question": "5x10",
    "answer": "50",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a13b3507-ff70-4d09-b7a2-d45019951c61"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "cd9856d6-98ec-4540-afc8-643b3f84fcdb"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x1",
    "answer": "6",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "52ae19cd-8049-423a-a04d-ea8c607c84de"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x2",
    "answer": "12",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "8eaa8c13-d3e1-4ece-b2bb-4d949a49a29c"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x3",
    "answer": "18",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "41db1d4b-753c-4c30-a5b1-b8cf470f9f4a"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x4",
    "answer": "24",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "5fce30c3-a7e4-4bd1-80d7-197f5d9e403a"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x5",
    "answer": "30",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "f2d49df7-b29d-41bf-8559-eb287b70a541"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x6",
    "answer": "36",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "3102d0ae-9dc5-4aff-8cd1-9b98074d2777"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x7",
    "answer": "42",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "46f60a18-eac1-4e34-b1d1-e6b94a03b77a"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x8",
    "answer": "48",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "011cd792-80a1-42c7-b041-9886ad35a9f8"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x9",
    "answer": "54",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a53d6b08-d363-479c-9b6a-e319ced987c6"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x10",
    "answer": "60",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "9ecde525-1e15-4f01-b97b-0c946b0e5ae7"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "92b242e3-090c-4d91-9495-6dd5b787be38"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x1",
    "answer": "7",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "d5115cda-bb4b-4b8c-b780-4bb301340d2c"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x2",
    "answer": "14",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "143eb4c4-ce38-4bdf-aee1-3fdd74c869e1"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x3",
    "answer": "21",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a0809210-69f6-4ae6-9464-865a6467d028"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x4",
    "answer": "28",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "57515485-98c2-4b94-9c0a-b130dd430c57"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x5",
    "answer": "35",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "e67a2d87-3707-407b-b3f3-c62edeeea8c3"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x6",
    "answer": "42",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "0cf7f9a7-a95e-4262-a908-1eedbb3d8d57"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x7",
    "answer": "49",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "fbbe18b1-8080-402d-bb7e-0e66f6d1ecdd"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x8",
    "answer": "56",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "9381c6f5-b36b-4dcf-af14-f503e665af5e"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x9",
    "answer": "63",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "0c7a9f96-ff6b-4faa-b074-ff232922d169"
  },
  {
    "question": "7x10",
    "answer": "70",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "22ed2f10-0cd3-42e7-b3ed-edd2c4a6a396"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "1607575c-a4d5-4608-9266-6e00c05dd9de"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x1",
    "answer": "8",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "c8f629d9-f111-426e-b907-dcec74784f22"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x2",
    "answer": "16",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "34556a08-3cee-4be0-b9d8-96c511de3f78"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x3",
    "answer": "24",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "70853bc7-5bd1-460a-8823-fc8f2a8acdbb"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x4",
    "answer": "32",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "04c5d3de-1306-45b3-9ece-eaa28ad241f8"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x5",
    "answer": "40",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "d05ca2bc-17f8-4c2a-86ee-d7f007a41f2a"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x6",
    "answer": "48",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "30c48a3b-4c03-40a8-af73-d5c68035ed26"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x7",
    "answer": "56",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "8c4ba651-646f-468a-92d4-86dc197a002e"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x8",
    "answer": "64",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "52ebe06a-dbb2-43b5-a54f-98f7d8e2a503"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x9",
    "answer": "72",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "83b1fb8c-6675-46a1-9e99-482e91a73d5b"
  },
  {
    "question": "8x10",
    "answer": "80",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "6b36b1cd-b0f4-40cd-8d66-96b931bdcede"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "32bdd926-f94b-4cb4-a545-ceaacec78629"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x1",
    "answer": "9",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "38614d8c-cb1d-4d28-8dcc-7cfe9af53573"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x2",
    "answer": "18",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a9f352d1-62d1-4278-a4a9-e760459537f3"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x3",
    "answer": "27",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "1459e242-859c-47a3-92c1-dfbadd15a405"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x4",
    "answer": "36",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "7521301f-dd0a-42ce-80b5-f96e2a839ce4"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x5",
    "answer": "45",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "4ed1aa49-8e9e-4cb2-a377-f8a7a6fdccae"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x6",
    "answer": "54",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "9aa28400-f40d-473a-897d-ab04ab36c3cb"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x7",
    "answer": "63",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "5894fc72-c82c-43bc-834f-23fd7106cf66"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x8",
    "answer": "72",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "2ef6d0c6-7364-4228-93e6-b65961b99e0a"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x9",
    "answer": "81",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "9cc901ec-23dd-4e58-988a-e0e51f1b2afd"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x10",
    "answer": "90",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "825483e7-b4b7-42cd-a877-63be78f4fae8"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x0",
    "answer": "0",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "0f206f86-6152-452c-b04b-58a490477701"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x1",
    "answer": "10",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "e9104dbf-354a-42c4-a48a-00f92be54518"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x2",
    "answer": "20",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a0355b4d-d1b2-4a88-813a-105a91b606e8"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x3",
    "answer": "30",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "38c8bae4-e5b5-4c38-9b06-81b349fbeca0"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x4",
    "answer": "40",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "1692799f-2908-4ad6-be08-9055cf4485d0"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x5",
    "answer": "50",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "20e6ee36-55c2-4966-a33f-a3da8b14fafc"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x6",
    "answer": "60",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "a770eab2-ef4a-4651-a001-805e7a8c6139"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x7",
    "answer": "70",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "e6fc384b-189c-4983-9ba0-15d4b9659fb8"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x8",
    "answer": "80",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "c44ac520-e7fe-42d1-a650-dbf6812bde17"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x9",
    "answer": "90",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "fb48f559-54a0-4217-9766-0b8d32eb49c3"
  },
  {
    "question": "10x10",
    "answer": "100",
    "tags": [
      "zoe"
    ],
    "id": "327d75d8-5c6c-4a8f-bbb4-e4c11e18b310"
  }
]